NADIIA AVRAMCHUK

101 Hazelville Road, West Midlands, England B28 9QD Home: +447450492265; email: avramchuk@hotmail.com

PERSONAL STATEMENT

A highly skilled and hardworking individual with over 8 years successful management and administrative experience. Fluent in Ukrainian and Russian languages. With strong document control, IT and communicational skills. Looking for the right opportunity to bring skills and experience to the purpose and further success.

Personal qualities: responsible, hardworking, creative, able to operate fast and within deadlines, fast learner, team player, able to act as a leader, diligent, conscientious, non-smoker.

SKILLS

- Document control: Sales Orders, Invoices, Receipts, Time sheets;
- Strong IT skills (Internet, MS Word, Excel, Sage, PowerPoint, Email, TSheets, Notes, Publisher, Adobe);
- Website operation and advertising;
- Market assessment and analysis;

- Office administration and general management skills;
- Operation with Clients' queries;
- Excellent technology (equipment) skills;
- Translations from/to English-Ukrainian-Russian languages;
- Team motivation and development.

WORK HISTORY

09/2018 to 03/2019

Office Manager

Kiara Sky Professional Nails – Birmingham, UK

- Was fully responsible for wholesalers' orders: order processing in Excel and Sage, stock confirmation, invoicing, dispatch control;
- Provided full document control: Sales Orders, Invoices, Receipts;
- Operated with Clients' queries;
- Participated in Beauty Exhibitions in London;
- Coordinated company's websites: fulfilled with products information, updates, links;
- Created and managed adverts, newsletters and notifications;
- Operated with Youtube channel and Facebook page;
- Was responsible for the overseeing and co-ordination the daily operational functions of the office;

12/2013 to 03/2018

Administrator/Office Manager

QuickAndQuality construction services Ltd – Bicester, UK

My position as an Administrative Manager in QuickAndQuality construction services also included basic marketing, HR and full document control duties.

- Was responsible for creation and operation of company's presentations, publications, adverts, events;
- Coordinated staff scheduling, mentoring, team motivation schemes;
- Organised and proceeded all paperwork (including company correspondence, expenses, time sheets, invoices, reports);
- Operated with company's database;
- Screened applicants' CVs and held both phone and in-person interviews;
- Finished projects: Cote brasserie in Brighton, Windsor and Glasgow, Five Guys Manchester;

07/2007 to 09/2009

Marketing Manager

Thomas & Adamson International Ltd - Kiev, Ukraine

My position as a Marketing Manager in Thomas & Adamson International used to cover marketing and HR duties, including general office control.

Marketing manager duties included:

- market monitor and research (online, telephone, publications);
- company presentations;
- creation and publication of marketing literature and adverts;
- operation with company website (fulfilling, updating, promotion).

HR duties included:

- staff research (screening CVs and coordination both phone and in-person interviews);
- scheduling and mentoring;
- organisation and coordination of company's events and entertainments;
- acting as an interpreter and translator.

07/2006 to 07/2007

Office Manager

Thomas & Adamson International Ltd - Kiev, Ukraine

- Was fully responsible for the overseeing and co-ordination the daily operational functions of the office;
- Including, but not limited to co-ordinating diaries and arranging meetings;
- Maintained clean and tidy reception and guest areas;
- Coordinated domestic and international travel arrangements, including booking flights, hotels and transport.
- Operated with documentation, including office expenses spreadsheets, time sheets for executives and employees, invoices, contracts, etc; all documentation and correspondence was held in English language;
- Ordered and distributed office supplies while adhering to a fixed office budget;
- Entered client and project information into the databases;
- Coordinated communication channels: calls, emails, faxes, letters, cards;
- Acted as an interpreter during meetings with international guests and provided documents translations.

EDUCATION

2010 Bachelor of Psychology; Honours degree: Psychology

Kiev city Pedagogical University after B. D. Hrinchenko - Kiev, Ukraine Considered comparable to British Bachelor Honours degree standard by NARIC

2005 **Bachelor of Philology: Philology**

Kiev National linguistic University - Kiev, Ukraine

Considered comparable to British Bachelor Ordinary degree standard by NARIC

2002 **Secondary Education Exam**

Kiev Primary Teachers' college by K. D. Ushynskyy - Kiev, Ukraine

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION:

Netcom (UK) Level 1 IT course Certificate;

"Profit" Centre (Kiev, Ukraine) Marketing course Certificate (96 hours); References available on request.